Permission Agreement of Printer Driver Installation


This agreement is to permit you to install the printer driver. Before installing printer driver, please read this agreement seriously. If you installed the software, in our opinion, you have agreed and promised that you will abide this agreement. If you don't agree anyone item, please don't install or stop using the software immediately.


1, Usage Permission
-This software only apply to the dot matrix, thermal POS printer, portable and panel printer.
-After you agreed this, we permit you to use the software.
-We don't sell the software to you, only permit you to install it.
-You have to guarantee: Beyond this agreement item,please don't use, copy, modify, hire or attorn this software, even any part of it. 


2, Property
This software is protected by <<Copyright Law of The People's Republic of China>>, <<Exclusive Law of The People's Republic of China>> and other correlative law, statute and treaty of intellectual property rights.


3, Right
You may use the software inside of the promissory bound.


4, Obligation

You can not operate this software, as below
-Sell, hire this whole software or any part of the software
-Make or provide any registration and cracking programme
-Amend, translate, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or disorganization and disassembly
-Delete any special information or label on this software and the copy
-Delete any copyright information or label on this software and the copy


5, Obligation Finity

Using this software, you bear the risk by yourself. Whether or not following this agreement, it may happen the profit loss, usability disappearing, business intermiting, or any indirect, special, thunderbolt or inevitable damage, we don't bear any obligation, even if we know this circs will happen.


6, Applying Law

This software is protected by these law and statute, as below: <<Copyright Law of The People's Republic of China>>, <<Exclusive Law of The People's Republic of China>>, << Intellectual Property Protection Statute>>, international copyright treaty and other law of intellectual property and treaty.


7, Agreement Effectiveness

During using this software, this agreement have force adeffect all the time. If you disobey anyone item in this software, we remaind right to terminate the licence at any moment. When we terminate the licence, you must destroy this software and copies immediately.


8, Abide Acceptance
Thus, we defaulted that you have read this agreement seriously and understood it completely, agreed and promised to abide every prescriptive item in this agreement.

